# Jignesh Ranpariya

Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India



jignesh.ranpariya91@gmail.com



9737649878



linkedin.com/in/jignesh-ranpariya-36368682

## **Summary**

Experienced Information Technology Executive with a demonstrated history of working in the pharmaceuticals industry, engineering industry and service base industry. Skilled in ERP Implementations, Networking, Leadership, Hardware, and Business Process Improvement. Strong information technology professional with a Master of Computer Applications (M.C.A.) focused in Computer and Information Sciences and Support Services from Shri Brahmanand Institute Of Management and Computer Science.

## **Experience**



## 罫 IT Manager

Sainest Tubes Pvt. Ltd.

Nov 2020 - Present (7 months +)

- Server administration, IT Security / Firewall /ERP.
- Maintain IT infrastructure (Software/Hardware/Network) smoothly and without any interruption.
- Update existing system and make it more flexible.
- Providing Guidance & support to staff for ERP.
- Implementation of security policy and measurement.
- Performing technical analysis & get ERP customized accordingly.
- Manage overall IT operations & provide solution.
- Design Develop Application as per requirement & support.

## ERP Implementation Consultant

SourcePro Infotech Pvt. Ltd.

Aug 2019 - Jun 2020 (11 months)

- Interact with the technical project team members responsible for developing reports, interfaces,
- Manage multiple clients and issues.
- Define testing scenarios and develop test scripts.
- Develop end-user documentation and training materials.
- Work with client online support to research and resolve application issues.
- Support clients with the execution of test scripts.
- Analyzed client-reported Financials, Supply Chain, Manufacturing, Sales or Projects issues, and resolve them in a timely and professional manner.
- Deliver end-user ERP training in technical and functional.
- Manage G-suite domain and company website.
- Windows troubleshooting, Upgrades and Patch management.
- Hardware & Networking and Software installation.
- User roles and permission, Active directory.
- Manage IT asset and CCTV.
- Manage windows server and User backup.



### Akhandjyot Group

Dec 2018 - Jul 2019 (8 months)

- Manage ERP system like Microsoft dynamics AX-2012 and HRMS Payroll System
- Provide end user ERP training as a technical & functional.
- Windows troubleshooting, Upgrades and Patch management.
- Hardware & Networking and Software installation.
- User roles and permission, Active directory.

#### ažafran IT & ERP Executive

Azafran Innovacion Ltd, India

Jun 2015 - Dec 2018 (3 years 7 months)

- System admin, Hardware & Networking and Software installation.
- Provide end user IT support for iMac, Windows 10/7, office365/Office 2016/2013.
- Manage IT-Inventory,
- ERP support technical as well functional.
- User Right Management viz. User roles and permission, Active directory.
- Maintaining In-house applications like ERP, Payroll and CRM. Windows troubleshooting, Upgrades and Patch management.

## Software Support Engineer

Soham ERP Solution Pvt Ltd.

Jan 2015 - Jul 2015 (7 months)

- Solve customer technical & functional ERP issue over the call and remote control.
- ERP Supporting as functional and technical Issue.
- ERP implementation on client module wise.
- Provide ERP training like Sales, purchase, finance, production, planning, stores&inventory and quality.

#### **Education**

## Shri Brahmanand Institute Of Management and Computer Science

Master of Computer Applications (M.C.A.), Computer and Information Sciences and Support Services

2011 - 2014

## Shashtri Swami Shri Dharmjivandasji Institute Of Science & Computer College

Bachelor's Degree, Computer and Information Sciences, General 2008 - 2011

Bsc-IT

#### **Skills**

ERP Implementations • System Administration • Technical Support • Process Improvement • Troubleshooting • Computer Hardware Troubleshooting • Software Installation • Customer Relationship Management (CRM) • Microsoft Office • Active Directory